<vtydoc xmlns='urn:osmocom:xml:libosmocore:vty:doc:1.0'>
  <!-- authentication -->
  <node id='0'><hide /></node>
  <node id='2'><hide /></node>
  <node id='8'><hide /></node>


  <node id='view'>
    <description>The view node is the default node when connecting to the
    VTY interface. This node does not require any additional
    permission and allows to introspect the application.</description>
  </node>

  <node id='enable'>
    <description>The enable node is a privileged node, allowing to make changes
    to the configuration and to access further commands like 'configure'.
    All commands seen on the view node are also available here.</description>
  </node>

  <node id='config'>
    <description>The config node is the root for all configuration commands,
    which are identical to the config file format. Changes made on the telnet
    VTY can be made persistent with the 'write file' command.</description>
  </node>
  <node id='config-log'>
    <child_of nodeid='config' />
    <description>The log node is commonly available in all Osmocom programs and
    allows configuring logging to stderr and/or log files, including logging
    category and level filtering as well as output formatting options.
    Note that the 'logging enable' command is required to make logging commands
    available on the telnet VTY.</description>
  </node>
  <node id='9'>
    <child_of nodeid='4' />
    <name>E1/J1/T1 Configuration Node</name>
    <description>This is the configuration for E1/J1/T1/IP configuration
    for mISDN, DAHDI or IP based connectivity.</description>
  </node>

  <common>
    <command id='logging enable'>
      <description>This command is required to make logging commands available
      on the telnet VTY.</description>
    </command>
    <command id='logging filter all (0|1)'>
      <description>Disable/enable general log output on a given target.
      Typically, 'logging filter all 1' allows to see the usual log output on a
      given target. Setting to '0' can be useful when logging to the telnet VTY
      console: mute all log output to allow typing VTY commands on the telnet
      prompt without interference from log output; 'logging filter all 1' then
      re-enables logging in the same log output configuration as before.

      Some applications provide more specific filters, e.g. to log a given IMSI
      only. To employ such filters, set 'logging filter all 0' to disable
      general logging, and then enable a more specific filter instead.
      </description>
    </command>
  </common>
</vtydoc>
